<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Free IT Solutions - online solutions for IT problems</title>
    <link>http://www.freeitsolutions.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Free IT Solutions - online solutions for IT problems</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.freeitsolutions.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Effective Methods To Deal With Copyright Infringement In 2019</title>
      <link>http://www.freeitsolutions.com/seo/copyright-infringement/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.freeitsolutions.com/seo/copyright-infringement/</guid>
      <description>If you are an online content creator for your blog or website, if you write content, create images or videos, your content was probably stolen at least once.
  This can be very frustrating especially because the site publishing the stolen content without your permission might get all the credit you worked so hard to produce.
  Not only that, but your SEO efforts might go down the drain and in the end you loose money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Online Code Syntax Checkers and Formatters</title>
      <link>http://www.freeitsolutions.com/web-development/code-syntax-checker-formatters/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.freeitsolutions.com/web-development/code-syntax-checker-formatters/</guid>
      <description>Code syntax checkers and formatters are tools that any web developer should keep close. Code syntax validation and code formatting are tasks that are part of all developers workflow.
 You know how it is,
Either you take over code written by somebody else, or code is generated from various applications. Manual source code review is not really fun. Even if you know how to fix syntax errors, wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be more efficient to let an automated tool do it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10&#43; Free Online Keyword Suggestion Tools</title>
      <link>http://www.freeitsolutions.com/seo/online-keyword-suggestion-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.freeitsolutions.com/seo/online-keyword-suggestion-tools/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s the truth:
 Doing keyword research for search engine optimization is crucial for getting a your website to rank higher. But what does keyword research actually mean?
  Basically, it means trying to guess which keywords and combination of keywords will attract the most traffic. Since guessing is not a science and SEO is, let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at how to do keyword research like a PRO for free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://www.freeitsolutions.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.freeitsolutions.com/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>